let COMPUTER_SUBJECT = {
	'subject_name':'Computer',
	'len':5,
	'0':{
		'question':'Arrange in ascending order the units of memory TB, KB, GB, MB ',
		'option1':'TB>MB>GB>KB',
		'option2':'MB>GB>TB>KB',
		'option3':'TB>GB>MB>KB',
		'option4':' GB>MB>KB>TB',
		'correct':'3'
	},
	'1':{
		'question':'Computer Moniter is also known as : ',
		'option1':'DVU',
		'option2':'UVD',
		'option3':'VDU',
		'option4':'CCTV',
		'correct':'3'
	},
	'2':{
		'question':'Which one of these also known as read/write memory ?',
		'option1':'ROM',
		'option2':'RAM',
		'option3':'DVD',
		'option4':'Hard disk',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'3':{
		'question':'Eight Bits make up a ',
		'option1':'byte',
		'option2':'megabyte',
		'option3':'killobyte',
		'option4':'None',
		'correct':'1'
	},
	'4':{
		'question':'Which one is the result of the output given by a computer ',
		'option1':'Data',
		'option2':'Istruction',
		'option3':'Information',
		'option4':'Excursion',
		'correct':'3'
	},
}
let CHEMISTRY_SUBJECT = {
	'subject_name':'Chemistry',
	'len':5,
	'0':{
		'question':'Heavy metal pollution of water is caused by :',
		'option1':'Acid Plants',
		'option2':'Paints',
		'option3':'Wood Burning',
		'option4':'Domestic Sewage',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'1':{
		'question':'Due to rusting the weight of iron:',
		'option1':'Decreases',
		'option2':'Increases',
		'option3':'Remains same',
		'option4':'uncertain',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'2':{
		'question':'The oil used in the froth floatation process is',
		'option1':'Cocunut oil',
		'option2':'Olive oil',
		'option3':'Kerosene',
		'option4':'Pine oil',
		'correct':'4'
	},
	'3':{
		'question':'Which of the following is the main ingredient of cement?',
		'option1':'Limestone',
		'option2':'Silica Clay',
		'option3':'Gypsum',
		'option4':'Ash',
		'correct':'3'
	},
	'4':{
		'question':'Which one of the following is not used to dope a semiconductor ?',
		'option1':'Al',
		'option2':'B',
		'option3':'In',
		'option4':'Au',
		'correct':'4'
	},
}
let PHYSICS_SUBJECT = {
	'subject_name':'Physics',
	'len':5,
	'0':{
		'question':'A man presses more weight on earth at :',
		'option1':'Sitting position',
		'option2':'Standing Position',
		'option3':'Lying Position',
		'option4':'None of these',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'1':{
		'question':'Young\'s modulus is the property of',
		'option1':'Gas only',
		'option2':'Solid and Liquids',
		'option3':'Liquid only',
		'option4':'Solid only',
		'correct':'4'
	},
	'2':{
		'question':'Product of Force and Velocity is called:',
		'option1':'Work',
		'option2':'Power',
		'option3':'Energy',
		'option4':'Momentum',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'3':{
		'question':'With the increase of pressure, the boiling point of any substance',
		'option1':'Increases',
		'option2':'Decreases',
		'option3':'Remains Same',
		'option4':'Becomes zero',
		'correct':'1'
	},
	'4':{
		'question':'Which law is also called the law of inertia ?',
		'option1':'Newton\'s first law',
		'option2':'Newton\'s second law',
		'option3':'Newton\'s third law',
		'option4':'None of these',
		'correct':'1'
	},
}
let MATHEMATICS_SUBJECT = {
	'subject_name':'Mathematics',
	'len':5,
	'0':{
		'question':'Evan wants to measure the length of his room. Which unit of measure is appropriate to measure thelength of his room?',
		'option1':'Centimeter',
		'option2':'Foot',
		'option3':'Inch',
		'option4':'Millimeter',
		'correct':'2'
	},
	'1':{
		'question':'What is 3/9 in simplest form?',
		'option1':'1/3',
		'option2':'2/9',
		'option3':'3/2',
		'option4':'3/1',
		'correct':'1'
	},
	'2':{
		'question':'Mrs. Perkins makes study guides for her class of 21 students. She uses 252 sheets of paper. Howmany sheets of paper are in each study guide?',
		'option1':'12 sheets',
		'option2':'231 sheets',
		'option3':'273 sheets',
		'option4':'2000 sheets',
		'correct':'1'
	},
	'3':{
		'question':'n the expression 15-n, which value of n results in the greatest difference?',
		'option1':'5',
		'option2':'10',
		'option3':'15',
		'option4':'0',
		'correct':'4'
	},
	'4':{
		'question':'What is the value of w in the equation 116 - w = 95?',
		'option1':'19',
		'option2':'10',
		'option3':'116',
		'option4':'21',
		'correct':'4'
	},
}
var database = {
	'1':MATHEMATICS_SUBJECT,
	'2':PHYSICS_SUBJECT,
	'3':CHEMISTRY_SUBJECT,
	'4':COMPUTER_SUBJECT,
}